Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
21-2-1620
David L. Call, 1932-
68.6 cubic ft.
Minutes, reports, statements, correspondence, speeches and other items.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of Dean David L. Call include materials pertaining to various departments of the college; other colleges at Cornell University; the Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York; the Cornell Board of Trustees and administration; Cornell Plantations; SUNY; CALS Alumni Association; Isles of Shoals; the Sea Grant Institute; Boyce Thompson Institute; New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets; New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives; the Council of Agricultural Organizations; Agway, Inc., Agricultural Resources Commission; and the Environmental Protection Agency.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dean, New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences (CALS), 1977-1995.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of Dean David L. Call include materials pertaining to various departments of the college; other colleges at Cornell University; the Agricultural Experiment Station in Geneva, New York; the Cornell Board of Trustees and administration; Cornell Plantations; SUNY; CALS Alumni Association; Isles of Shoals; the Sea Grant Institute; Boyce Thompson Institute; New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets; New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives; the Council of Agricultural Organizations; Agway, Inc., Agricultural Resources Commission; and the Environmental Protection Agency. Included are minutes, reports, statements, correspondence, speeches and other items concerning pesticide use and environmental issues, bovine hormone use, agricultural extension, rural development, pest control, migrant labor, agricultural policies, soil and water conservation, legislative bills, investments, land-grant affairs, academic funding and tuition, development, budgets, admissions, faculty salaries and tenure, staff relations, affirmative action and minority affairs, sex discrimination, education programs, libraries, computers, campus planning and development, university policies and procedures, and other matters. Major correspondents include Frank Rhodes, Henry Uihlein, and Roy Carver. Also photographs and items relating to his retirement. Also materials relating to the Unimal and a Chinese vase presented to Call by President Lee Teng-hui of Taiwan.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Call, David L., 1932-; Carver, Roy.; Lee, Teng-hui; Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor.; Uihlein, Henry.; Agricultural Resources Commission.; Agway Inc.; Cornell Plantations.; Cornell University--Administration.; Cornell University--Admission.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Employees.; Cornell University--Faculty--Salaries, pensions, etc.; Cornell University--Finance.; Cornell University--Planning.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.; Cornell University. Hudson Basin Project.; Cornell University. Cooperative Extension.; Council of Agricultural Organizations.; New York (State). Dept. of Agriculture and Markets.; New York Sea Grant Institute.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Administration.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Admission.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Alumni.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Buildings.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Curricula.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Employees.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Faculty--Salaries, pensions, etc.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Finance.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Libraries.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Planning.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Agricultural Experiment Station.; New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives.; New York State Farm Electrification Council.; United States.Environmental Protection Agency.; University of the State of New York.
Subjects:
Affirmative action programs.; Agricultural administration.; Agricultural colleges.; Agricultural extension work.; Agricultural law and legislation.; Agriculture, Cooperative.; Agriculture--Study and teaching.; Agriculture--New York (State); Campus planning.; Conservation of natural resources.; Pests--Control.; Rural development.; Soil conservation.; State universities and colleges.; Hormones in animal nutrition--Law and legislation.; Sex discrimination.; Migrant labor.; Minorities--Employment.; Minorities--Education.
Places:
Isles of Shoals (Me. and N.H.)
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Speeches.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Boxes 1-67 restricted to permission of the Dean's Office, New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Box 68-69 and MU-1743 are open.
CONTAINER LIST
- A (General Correspondence), 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abt Associates Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academic Freedom andResponsibility, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Accessory Instruction, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Acid Precipitation, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Admissions, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Admissions Referrals, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Advisory Council on Agriculture, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Affirmative Action, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AgFax, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- AGNET (AGricultural computer NETwork), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Ag-PAC (ALS Positive Action Council), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Agribusiness Council, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agricultural Districts, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Districts, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Agricultural Economics, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Economics, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forums, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Organizations, Council, 1977-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Resources Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Statistics, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Agriculture in Economy, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Agriculture, Secretary of, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Agronomy, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Agway, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Aldicarb (Pesticide), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- ALS Fund, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Alumni Association, CALS, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Alumni Office, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Animal Science, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Animal Science, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Aquaculture, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Arnot Forest, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Associate Dean Search, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Atmospheric Sciences, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Audit, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Audit, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Awards, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Awards, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- B (General Correspondence), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Barbados Sheep Project, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Benefits, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- BESS (People's Development Corporation), 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- BESS (People's Development Corporation), 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Biomass, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Board of Trustees, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Budget, Division of, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- C (General Correspondence), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Census, Agriculture, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Children's Tuition Scholarship Plan, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- China, People's Republic of, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- China, People's Republic of, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Climatologist (for NYS), 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Climatologist (for NYS), 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Committee to Advise on Ways of IncreasingOutside Research Support to the University, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Communication Arts, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Computer Activity Group (CAG), 1978 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Computers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Computers, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Computing Advisory Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Cook, Constance (Vice President, Land Grant Affairs), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Cooperative Extension, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Cooperative Extension, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Cooperative Extension--Director Search, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cooperative Extension--4-H, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cooperative Extension--New York City, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Cooperative Extension--New York City, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cooperative Extension--Small Business, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Cornell Plantations, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Cornell Plantations, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Counsel, Cornell University, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- County Agents, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Culver Farm, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- D (General Correspondence), 1953-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Dairy Days, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Dean's Council, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Dean's Statutory Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Dean of College of Agriculture Search Committee, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- DNA Research Requirements, 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- E (General Correspondence), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Endrin (Pesticide), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Endrin (Pesticide), 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Energy, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Energy, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Enrollments, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Entomology, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Entomology, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Environmental Sciences & Forestry, College of, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Environmental Mediation Center, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Equine Program, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- F (General Correspondence), 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Faculty Honors, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Farm Credit Banks of Springfield, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Farms, Small, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Finance & Business Office, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Fleet Cars, 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Floriculture & Ornamental Horticulture, Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Food Issues, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Food Issues, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Food Safety Council, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Food Safety Council, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Food Science, Dept. of / Institute of Food Science, 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Food Science, Dept. of / Institute of Food Science, 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Fume Hoods Laboratory, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Fund Raising Policy, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- G (General Correspondence), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Gasohol, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Goals, Aspirations, & Priorities, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Golden Nematode Amendment, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Gourman Report, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Graduate School, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Grievance Procedure, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Grievance Procedure, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- H (General Correspondence), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Health Resources, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Honorarium, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Human Ecology, College of, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Industrial Labor Relations (ILR), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Institute of Food Science, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Instruction, Office of, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Instruction, Office of, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Integrated Pest Management (IPM), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- International Agricultural Development (IAD), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- International Agricultural Development (IAD), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- International Programs, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- International Rice Research Institute (Nyle Brady, Director General), 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- International Studies, Center of, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- International Studies, Center of, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Ithaca & Cornell University, 1977-1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- J (General Correspondence), 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Job Placement, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- K (General Correspondence), 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Kellogg Foundation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Kennedy, William--Provost, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Kennedy, William--Provost, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- L (General Correspondence), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Land Use Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor (Robert H Fook), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Local Government Program, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Lab, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Media Services, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Media Services, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Microbiology, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Miner Institute, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Minority Education Council, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Minority Program for CALS, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Myers, W.I.Professorship, 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- N (General Correspondence), 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Natural Resources, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- New York Farmers, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- NYS Agricultural Experiment Station--Geneva, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- NYS Agricultural Society, 1978-1981 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- NYS Dept. of Agriculture and Markets, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- NYS Assembly, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- NYS Farm Bureau, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- NYS Food and Energy Council, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- NYS Food and Energy Council, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- NYS Dept. of Environmental Conservation, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- NYS Dept. of Environmental Conservation, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- NYS Horticultural Society, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- NYS Soil & Water Conservation Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- O (General Correspondence), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Overhead, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- P (General Correspondence), 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Plant Breeding, Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Pomology (Ithaca & Geneva), Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Pomology & Viticulture (Dr. K. Frank), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Poultry Husbandry, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Poultry Science, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Poultry Science, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Pro-Fac Cooperative, Inc., 1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs, Office of, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- R (General Correspondence), 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Research, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Research, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Rhodes, Frank, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Rural Sociology, Dept. of, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Salaries, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- SUNY--Advisory Council, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- SUNY--Agriculture & Tech Colleges, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- SUNY--Campuses, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- SUNY--Cornell Relations, 1967-1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- SUNY--Council of Presidents, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- SUNY--Institutional Research, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Research & Graduate Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- SUNY--Wharton, Clifton--Chancellor, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- SUNY--Women, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- T (General Correspondence), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Technical Assessment, Office of, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Technical Assessment, Office of, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Technical Assistance Center, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Temporary State Commission on the Real Property Tax, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Title V, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Tropical Studies, Organization of, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Uihelein, Henry (Donor), 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- United Way, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- University Council, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- University Development, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- USDA (US Dept. of Agriculture), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- USDA Competitive Grants Policy Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- USDA Competitive Grants Policy Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Urban Horticulture Institute, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Vegetable Crops, Dept. of, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Veterinary College, 1965-1979 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- W (General Correspondence), 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Wisconsin Review, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Adirondack Park Research, 1978-1982 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Administrative Operations, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Administrative Operations, 1978-1981 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Admissions, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- AgPAC, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Agribusiness Council, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Districts, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Economics Lecture, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Organizations, Council of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Water Management Program, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Agriculture, Advisory Council on, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Agriculture, Division of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Agriculture, Division of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Agronomy, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Agway, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Alumni Association, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Animal Science, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Arnot Forest, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Atmospheric Science Unit, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- B (General Correspondence), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Barlow, J.R.--Assistant to the President, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Barlow, J.R.--Assistant to the President, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bean & Cowpea CRSP (Collaborative Research Support Program), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Belize--Roy Carver Ranch (Donor), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Belize--Roy Carver Ranch (Donor), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Belize--Roy Carver Ranch (Donor), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Belize--Roy Carver Ranch (Donor), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Biometrics, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Board of Trustees, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Board of Trustees, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research--Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research--Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- C (General Correspondence), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- CAHA (Council of Administrative Heads of Agriculture), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- CAHA (Council of Administrative Heads of Agriculture), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- CAHA (Council of Administrative Heads of Agriculture), 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- CAHA (Council of Administrative Heads of Agriculture), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- CAHA Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- CARET (Committee for Agricultural Research, Extension and Teaching), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- CARET (Committee for Agricultural Research, Extension and Teaching), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- CARET (Committee for Agricultural Research, Extension and Teaching), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Children's Tuition Scholarship Plan, 1981-1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- China, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- China, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- China Trip, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- China Trip, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- CISER (Cornell Institute for Social & Economic Research), 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Cohn Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Communication Arts, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Computers, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Computing Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Congress Members, 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cook, Constance (Vice President, Land Grant Affairs), 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Cook, Constance (Vice President, Land Grant Affairs), 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cook, Constance (Vice President, Land Grant Affairs), 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Cooke, W. Donald (Vice President for Research), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Cooke, W. Donald (Vice President for Research), 1978-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Cooperative Extension, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Cornell Plantations, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Cornell Plantations, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Cornell Plantations, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Corporate Relations, Office of, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Corporate Relations, Office of, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Counsel, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Counsel, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Dairy Promotion Program, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Dean's Council, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Dean's Council, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Dean's Council, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Dean's Statutory Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Dean's Statutory Meetings, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Dean of Students, Office of, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Department Allocations of Positions, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Department & Section Chair Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Development & Alumni Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Development & Alumni Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Ecosystems Research Center, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Education, NYS Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Education Chairman Search, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Egner, Joan R. (Associate Dean), 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Egner, Joan R. (Associate Dean), 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Empire Farm Days, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Energy, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Entomology, Dept. of, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Environmental Research, Center for, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Equalization & Assessment, Division of, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Equal Opportunity, Office of, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Extension Biannual Conference, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)